zimmermannwear.com 2015-10-25

# Privacy

Zimmermann Wear Pty Ltd (ABN: 13062643609) and its related companies ( **Zimmermann, we, us, our** ) understands that your privacy is important and ensures that your personal information is handled in accordance with the _Privacy Act 1988_ (Cth) ( **Privacy Act** ).  This Privacy Policy explains how we manage personal information and the ways in which you may contact us about personal information we hold about you.

### Purposes for handling personal information

Personal information is information about you, such as your name, contact details and records of your dealings with us. We collect, hold, use and disclose personal information:

  1. to process transactions and deliver products to you
  2. to communicate with you
  3. to assess applications for employment
  4. to maintain our business records and to otherwise run our business
  5. for purposes disclosed to you and to which you have consented
  6. for purposes that you would otherwise reasonably expect, and
  7. for any other purposes required or permitted by law.

### Collection of your personal information

We collect personal information from our customers, business contacts, prospective employees and other individuals with whom we deal. We only collect personal information by lawful and fair means. We will collect your personal information through our interactions with you, such as when you make a purchase from us, where we communicate by telephone, mail, email, or when you enter your personal information on our website. In some cases, where it would be unreasonable or impracticable to obtain your personal information directly from you, we may seek to obtain it from a third party.

### Use and disclosure of your personal information

We will only use and disclose your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.  We may disclose your personal information to third parties including:

  1. our service providers (including IT services, financial institutions, mailing houses and distribution services)
  2. our related companies and other business partners
  3. our professional advisers (including lawyers, accountants and auditors)
  4. other parties as required or authorised by law.
  5. In so doing, we may disclose your personal information outside of Australia to related parties in the USA.

### Security of your personal information

We make all reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is stored securely, both in electronic and physical form, and otherwise protect it from misuse, interference and loss caused by unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.  We hold your personal information in both paper-based and electronic files.  Our employees and agents are obliged to treat any personal information held by us confidentially.

### Collection of website usage information

Our website utilises "cookies", which are pieces of data that are stored on your hard drive containing details about your use of our website.  Use of a cookie does not provide us with information about you that can be used to identify you. Rather, they anonymously track usage of our website, so that we can enhance users' experience of our website.  You may elect to reject cookies and still use our website, however in doing so, you may not be able to access certain pages.  
We also use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer our website, track use movements on our website, and gather broad demographic data for aggregate use, which we may share with our partners and advertisers.  We note that IP addresses are not linked to any information that could identify you.

### Accessing and correcting your personal information

You may access your personal information held by Zimmermann by contacting our office on +61 2 9697 9988 or [**onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com**](mailto:onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com). We will respond to all requests for access and on the rare occasions when we refuse access to your information, we will provide you with a written notice stating the reasons for our refusal.  We may seek to recover from you reasonable costs that we incur in providing you with access to any of the personal information that we hold about you.  
We seek to ensure that the personal information that we collect, hold and use is accurate, up-to-date and complete, and the personal information that we use and disclose to third parties is relevant. If you discover that there is an error, or if the personal information we hold about you is outdated, incomplete or irrelevant, please contact our office on +61 2 9697 9988 or [**onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com**](mailto:onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com). We are not obliged to correct any of your personal information if we do not agree that it requires correction. If we refuse to do so, we will provide you with a written notice stating the reasons for our refusal.

### Marketing

We may use your personal information, including your contact details, to provide you with relevant consumer information, notify you of products, store openings and offers that may be of interest to you as a valued Zimmermann customer or business associat.  You may opt out of receiving all or certain types of marketing information from us at any time by following the instructions at the bottom of our communications.  Alternatively, you may contact our head office on +61 2 9697 9988 or [**onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com**](mailto:onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com) if you do not wish your details to be used for marketing purposes.

### Questions and complaints

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the way in which we have handled your personal information you may contact us on +61 2 9697 9988 or [**onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com**](mailto:onlinestore@zimmermannwear.com) . We respond to all complaints as soon as possible.   
You may also lodge a complaint with the Office of Australian Information Commissioner by calling 1300 363 992 or sending an email to enquiries@oaic.gov.au.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Zimmermann may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice to you. The up-to-date version of our Privacy Policy is on our website.
